Hikmet Can Kufteoglu

Frontend Developer

https://hicaku.com

hikmet.kufteoglu(at)gmail.com

github.com/Spencehiko

in linkedin.com/in/hicaku/

A passionate Frontend Developer who is keen to learn new technologies. Worked over 3 years in different scale of companies and developed big scaled projects. Open to new ideas and willing to use my skills combined with well-thought projects. Looking forward to taking my current skills to upper levels and benefit both myself and the company I am working.

Work Experience

Huawei - Full Time

01/2021 - NOW

Frontend Developer

Currently I am working in Huawei as a frontend Developer. We developed several tools for Petal Maps. Although we had a small team of developers, we managed to overcome tough obstacles on our way. I won a Future Star Award at the end of 2021.

Location: Remote/Turkey Website: https://huawei.com/

Firmasoft - Part Time

12/2018 - 05/2021

Junior Full Stack Developer

In Firmasoft, the aim was to build CMSs,websites and mobile apps for our clients. I developed many websites and CMSs with our small team. I worked full-time on holidays and part-time on the rest.

Website: http://firmasoft.com/

Datapare - Part Time

06/2018 - 11/2018

Junior Frontend Developer

I learnt basics of web development and working in a fast paced, agile team. It was a startup and I worked fulltime on holidays and part-time on the rest.

Location: Istanbul/Turkey

Education

Graduate 06/2016 - 01/2021

Istanbul Technical University - Mathematics Engineering

2.97

Skills

Vue.js

★★★★★☆☆☆☆

Experience: 1-3 Years

I have been working with Vue.js for my current company and also I am developing personal apps to improve myself. At work we use Vue 2 with Vuex and in my personal projects I use Vue 3 (Composition API) with Pinia.

TypeScript

Experience: 1-3 Years



I have been working with TypeScript implemented in Vue.js and I have built global scale projects with it in my previous job experiences.

JavaScript

Experience: 3-5 Years

★★★★★★☆☆☆

I have been working on this subject for over 4 years and I have built global scale projects with it in my previous job experiences.

Tailwind CSS

Experience: < 1 Year

★★★★★☆☆☆☆

I am using Tailwind CSS in my personal projects and I have built several apps with it.

HTML/CSS

Experience: 3-5 Years

For many years, I have worked with HTML and CSS. I have a really good understanding of the correlation between them and I can code a design for the web page easily. I know LESS as well.

GitHub

Experience: 1-3 Years

★★★★★☆☆☆☆

I have the knowledge of Git commands. I have been using Sourcetree to visualize these actions, but I can use them on command line as well.

PHP & MySQL

Experience: 1-3 Years

 $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta$

I have worked with PHP and MySQL for over 2 years and I have built several CMSs with it. I am familiar with OOP and API structures of PHP. Also I have the knowledge of queries and data management in MySQL

Web Testing Tools

Experience: < 1 Year

 $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta \Delta$

I used Jest for unit testing and Cypress for end-to-end testing. I have the basic knowledge of them.

Languages

Turkish

English

References

Salih Kesepara - Frontend Team Lead at Huawei

salih.kesepara(at)huawei.com

Mustafa Tunç - CEO and Founder at Firmasoft

mustafatunc(at)firmasoft.com

Serkan Uz - CEO and Founder at Datapare

serkanuz(at)datapare.com